{
    "data": [
      
        {
            "question": "What are the features of React?",
            "choices":["Uses virtual DOM","Uses real DOM","Has no server side rendering","No data binding"],
            "answer": "Uses virtual DOM"
        },
        {
            "question": "Limitations of React?",
            "choices":["Full blown framework","React is just a library","Library is very small","Coding is easy"],
            "answer": "React is just a library"

        },

        {
            "question": "Difference between React and Angular",
            "choices":["React author is Facebook, while Angular author is Google","React author is Facebook, while Angular author is Google"],
            "answer": "React author is Facebook, while Angular author is Google"

        },

        {
            "question": "What is the arrow function in React?",
            "choices":["Allow to bind the context","Arrow functions are mostly useful while working with the lower order functions."],
            "answer": "Allow to bind the context"

        },

        {
            "question": "What are the different phases of React componentâ€™s lifecycle?",
            "choices":["Mounting Phase","Initial Rendering Phase", "Complete Phase"],
            "answer": "Initial Rendering Phase"

        },

        {
            "question": "DOM meaning",
            "choices":["Days On Market","Distributed Object Management", "Date of Maturity","Document Object Oriented"],
            "answer": "Document Object Oriented"

        },

        {
            "question": "List some of the cases when you should use Refs.",
            "choices":["Delete third-party DOM libraries","To trigger imperative animations"],
            "answer": "Initial Rendering Phase"

        },

        {
            "question": "What do you know about controlled components?",
            "choices":[" They take in the current values through props and then notify the changes via callbacks","Data is controlled by the parent component","They maintain their own state"],
            "answer": "Data is controlled by the parent component"

        },

        {
            "question": "What do you know about uncontrolled components?",
            "choices":["Refs are used to get their current values","They do not maintain their own state"],
            "answer": "Refs are used to get their current values"

        },

        {
            "question": "What can you do with HOC?",
            "choices":["Delete third-party DOM libraries","Code reuse, logic and bootstrap abstraction"],
            "answer": "Code reuse, logic and bootstrap abstraction"

        }

    ]
}